Guide to the Outdoor Advertising Associaiton of Connecticut Records, 1970-1996
The John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising & Marketing History David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library Duke University Durham, N.C., USA
Outdoor Advertising Associaiton of Connecticut records 1970-1996
David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library, Duke University
Outdoor Advertising Association of Connecticut
2.4 Linear Feet 1800 Items
Outdoor advertising professional organization in Connecticut in the 1970s-1990s.
Collection contains the organizational records of the Outdoor Advertising Association of Connecticut, primarily consisting of correspondence (1970-1987), rosters, bylaws, and other organizational files. Also included are files related to the Scenic Roadways project with the State of Connecticut, as well as lobbyist files and information on senate bills that may affect outdoor advertising. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising, and Marketing History.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Collection is open for research.
Researchers must register and agree to copyright and privacy laws before using this collection.
All or portions of this collection may be housed off-site in Duke University's Library Service Center. The library may require up to 48 hours to retrieve these materials for research use.
Please contact Research Services staff before visiting the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library to use this collection.
Provenance
The Outdoor Advertising Associaiton of Connecticut Records were received by the David M. Rubenstein Rare Book & Manuscript Library as a gift in 2007.
Biographical Note
Outdoor advertising professional organization in Connecticut in the 1970s-1990s.
Collection Overview
Collection contains the organizational records of the Outdoor Advertising Association of Connecticut, primarily consisting of correspondence (1970-1987), rosters, bylaws, and other organizational files. Also included are files related to the Scenic Roadways project with the State of Connecticut, as well as lobbyist files and information on senate bills that may affect outdoor advertising. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising, and Marketing History.
Subject Headings
These are searchable subject entries for this collection. Performing a search on these subjects in the Duke University Libraries online catalog will bring up other related research materials.
Outdoor Advertising Association of Connecticut
Advertising, Outdoor -- United States -- History -- 20th century
Advertising, Outdoor -- Connecticut
Contents of Collection
- Accession (2007-0209), 1970-1996, 4 Boxes
  Accession contains the organizational records of the Outdoor Advertising Association of Connecticut, primarily consisting of correspondence (1970-1987), rosters, bylaws, and other organizational files. Also included are files related to the Scenic Roadways project with the State of Connecticut, as well as lobbyist files and information on senate bills that may affect outdoor advertising. Acquired as part of the John W. Hartman Center for Sales, Advertising, and Marketing History.
  - Correspondence, 1970-1984 (Box 1)
  - Correspondence, 1985-1987 (Box 2)
  - By-laws and other organizational files
  - Scenic Landscapes files
  - Lobbyist files (Box 3)
  - Minutes
  - Organizational files
  - Organizational files (Box 4)
  - Files on Senate Bill No. 1068, 1989
  - Roster, 1991